TYLER WYLES

WEB DEV SKILLS

HTML5 · CSS3/SCSS · JavaScript · React ·

RESTful APISs · Firebase · Git/Github ·

Paired/Mob Programming •

Accesibility Standards

CREATIVE SKILLS

Figma · Adobe Photoshop ·

Adobe Illustrator · Lottie Animations

EDUCATION

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

City of Toronto

2022 - 2023

Ontario Real Estate Association

City of Toronto 2015 - 2016

Fitness & Health Promotion

Humber College 2012 - 2014

PASSIONS

Restoring Vintage Motorcycles

Front End Developer

CAREER SUMMARY

I'm a front-end developer who crafts visually stunning and accessible web designs using the power of CSS. My previous experience in the fast-paced real estate world has given me exceptional communication and problem-solving skills, which seamlessly translate to coding.

RECENT PROJECTS

Is the book better?

2023

2023

Collaborated with a team of 4, using Google Books API & TheMoviesDB API to build a React app comparing ratings for user-entered titles.

https://github.com/tywy87/book-vs-movie

Reel Movie Tracker

A user-friendly movie tracking application that simplifies the process of keeping track of watched movies and their ratings. Collaboratively built with Kyle Lau, the application leverages the Firebase API and is constructed using vanilla JavaScript to provide a seamless and intuitive user experience.

https://github.com/KyleKHL/reelMovieTracker

FIND ME ONLINE



LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tylerw yles/



GitHub

https://github.com/tywy87

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Coach/Mentor

2018 - Present

Lamerias Group - Our Neighbourhood Realty., Inc

Toronto, ON

Team leader and coach with experience in training and mentoring new agents, implementing sales techniques and introducing new processes to improve productivity and sales. Pursued continuing education courses to stay updated on the latest trends in the real estate market.

- Developed and implemented daily, weekly, and monthly goals to improve the sales techniques of new agents resulting in the "100 Days to Greatness" program
- Introduced new processes and techniques for time management, resulting in increased productivity and sales
- Monitored and evaluated the performance of new agents, providing ongoing feedback and coaching to improve their skills
- Collaborated with senior management to develop and implement strategies to improve overall team performance and achieve organizational goals
- Conducted training sessions and workshops to improve the skills and knowledge of new and existing agents

Sales Representative

2016 - 2018

RE/MAX Hallmark Realty

Toronto, ON

I provided clients with critical market information, legal requirements, pricing, and mortgage options to facilitate successful transactions. I balanced clients' needs with financial constraints, offering guidance on critical sale and purchase decisions.

• Developed and maintained strong relationships with clients, providing ongoing support and communication throughout the entire transaction process.